Game clips are videos of your gaming highlights.
Your clips can be up to five minutes long.
A quick way to capture a thirty-second clip any time you’re playing a game
is to double-tap the Xbox button, and then press X.
This captures the last thirty seconds as a clip that you can save or edit later.
To watch your clips, open the Game DVR app.
Keep your favorites by pressing the Menu button on your controller, then Save.
Clips you don’t save are deleted automatically after a while.
Snap the Game DVR to make longer recordings.
Double-tap the Xbox button,
go down to Snap an app,
and choose Game DVR.
You can capture clips after something happens,
or start recording before you do something.
To capture after, double-tap the Xbox button. Move right and select Game DVR.
Then choose End clip now and decide how far back you want the clip to start,
up to five minutes ago.
To start recording first, choose Start new clip, then Start recording.
To stop, double-tap the Xbox button again, switch to Game DVR,
then Stop Recording.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.